Everyone has one more fight in them
Rambo: Last Blood is a action, thriller, drama film directed by Adrian Grünberg.
After fighting his demons for decades, John Rambo now lives in peace on his family ranch in Arizona, but his rest is interrupted when
Gabriela, the granddaughter of his housekeeper María, disappears after crossing the border into Mexico to meet her biological father.
Rambo, who has become a true father figure for Gabriela over the years,
undertakes a desperate and dangerous journey to find her.
John Rambo, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Carmen, played by Paz Vega.
Hugo Martínez, played by Sergio Peris-Mencheta.
María Beltrán, played by Adriana Barraza.
Gabriela, played by Yvette Monreal.
Don Manuel, played by Joaquín Cosío.
Rambo: Last Blood is a 2019 American vigilante action film starring
Sylvester Stallone as Vietnam War veteran John Rambo.
Directed by Adrian Grünberg, the film serves as a sequel to Rambo
(2008), and the fifth installment in the Rambo film series.
The story sees Rambo traveling to Mexico to save his adopted niece, who has
been kidnapped by a Mexican cartel and forced into prostitution.
Paz Vega, Sergio Peris-Mencheta, Adriana Barraza, Yvette Monreal, Genie Kim aka
Yenah Han, Joaquín Cosío, and Óscar Jaenada star in supporting roles.
Plans for a fifth film were announced on and off again since 2008,
with different iterations developed and canceled.
The film was finally announced in May 2018, with Grünberg attached to direct.
Principal photography began in October 2018 in Bulgaria and Spain and ended
in December 2018, with additional photography in May 2019.
Brian Tyler returned to score the film.
Rambo: Last Blood was theatrically released on September 20, 2019, to negative reviews from critics, who criticized its script, graphic violence
and perceived racist and xenophobic attitudes towards Mexico, though the action sequences and Stallone's performance were praised.
The film grossed $91.5 million worldwide against a production budget of $50
million and print and advertisement costs of $30 million.
The film explores themes of post-traumatic stress disorder (ptsd),
arizona, human trafficking, affectation, sequel.
The tone is emotional and intense.